

OMER MUNK

• DETAILS •

Tel Aviv Israel +972 53 473 2242 omermunk95@gmail.com

> Date of birth 1995

Nationality Israeli, French

LINKS

LinkedIn

GitHub

SKILLS

Node.js, JavaScript, TypeScript

Python, Django, Flask

SQL, MongoDB, Redis

HTML, CSS, SaSS

Angular

React

Linux

Java

С

C#

Amazon Web Services
Google Cloud Services

HOBBIES

Chess, Guitar, Singing

LANGUAGES

Hebrew

English

PROFILE

Passionate about designing and developing web, server, database, and cloud solutions. My skills in problem solving, team work, and working under pressure, combined with my experience in education and business operations, enable me to excel in all stages of development, from design to deployment and maintenance. I have a diverse skill set with range of technologies. I am comfortable working independently or as part of a team. I am well-versed in the latest development tools and agile development methodologies, such as Scrum.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer at Moveo, Tel Aviv

April 2022 — Present

Designed and developed server, micro-services and database, for one of the top payments applications in Israel, with a scale of 2.5M users. Designed and developed an appointment setting web application and a server for a big private hospital in Tel Aviv . Worked with: NodeJS, React, Angular, Python, Flutter ,SQL, MongoDB, Redis, AWS, GCP, Jira products and Monday.

Lecturer at John Bryce Coding Academy, Tel Aviv

April 2022 — Present

Teaching academy students Python, Django, Flask and React

Co-Founder at MetaTech

Established full eLearning platform and managed business operations, including financial planning, customer relations, marketing, and employee development.

Freelance Full Stack Developer & Personal Tutor

December 2020

Developed small projects working as an independent developer. Taught academic Computer Science, Programming, Web development, Math and Physics, with over 700 hours of experience

EDUCATION

BSc Computer Science, The Open University, Tel Aviv

March 2021 — August 2023

Studied all my courses while working. About 1/3 of the courses left to finish. Computer Science GPA - 85

Python Full Stack Development Diploma, John Bryce Coding Academy, Tel Aviv 2021-2022

Software Engineering class, 5 units matriculation, Multidisciplinary High School, Hadera

2011 - 2014

★ MILITARY SERVICE

Captain, Company Commander, IDF

2015 - 2021

Managed and led a unit of 200 soldiers.